jobspire.net 2015-05-23

# Privacy Policy - Jobspire

* * *

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

  *  **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

  *  **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site.

  *  **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

    * To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
    * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
    * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
    * To quickly process your transactions.
    * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

We don't store details on our server.

  *  **Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

  *  **We use cookies to -**  

    * Help remember and process your payments.
    * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
    * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf but will never sell this information to any third party.
    * You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

  *  **If users disable cookies in their browser -**

If you disable cookies, some features will be disabled. It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

  *  **Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

  *  **Third party links**

We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.

  *  **California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more [here](http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf).

  *  **According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following -**

Users can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page. Users are able to change their personal information by logging in to their account, by chatting with us or sending us a ticket.

  *  **How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

  *  **Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**

It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking.

  *  **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. We do not specifically market to children under 13.

  *  **Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significantrole in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implementedis critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

  *  **In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur -**  

    * We will notify the users via email within 7 business days.
    * We will notify the users via in site notification within 7 business days.

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

  *  **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

  *  **We collect your email address in order to -**  

    * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
    * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders
    * We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
    * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

  *  **To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following -**  

    * NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
    * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
    * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
    * Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
    * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
    * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

  *  **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

60/45, 6th Cross, Cambridge Layout  
Bangalore, 560008  
Karnataka, India  
Email: mayya@jobspire.net | Phone: +919741863192

Last Edited on 3rd February, 2015.
